威尔 · 森塔斯: 所以，把解决方案二总结回到这个目标的核心。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So to summarize solution
two back to the core of the goal here.
就像我给我们所有人的奖励，只是，有趣的事情。
Like I gave those bonus pieces there for
all of us just, intriguing things.
使用原型链，使用 JavaScript prototype 或
Using the prototype chain,
using JavaScript prototype or
用户一号和用户二号,
feature that user one and user two,
从它们在用户创建器内部创建时开始访问
go access from when they were
created inside of user creator
创建的顺序给了他们的对象一个使用函数存储的键。
with the order to create which gave their
object a bond to use a function store.
当我运行用户 one.increment 并且没有找到它时,
When I ran user one.increment and
did not find it,
用户1的增量功能，我慌了吗？
the increment functionality of user one,
did I panic?
没有，我在原型链上向用户提供了原型参考
No, I headed up the proto reference
at the prototype chain to the user
函数存储在哪里我找到了增量，我运行它，问题与这？
function store where I found increment,
and I run it, problems with this?
没问题，很漂亮。
No problems, it's beautiful.
这有点像《星球大战》 ，你在面试中对面试官说:
It's a sort of Star Wars with you in
your interview said to your interviewer,
我更喜欢这样，因为我想对我的文章进行更细致的控制
I prefer because I want more fine
grained control over my writing of my
我倾向于尝试和遵循这种方法。
oxygen that I tend to try and
follow this approach.
他们会去，他们会想最坏的情况。
And they're gonna go,
they're gonna think the worst.
但是，同时，他们会去，令人印象深刻。
But, at the same time,
they're gonna go, impressive.
我最好说我同意。
I better say I agree.
他们会说，是的，我也是，是的。
They're gonna go, yes, me too, yes.
他们不是说这是正确的方式，这当然不是标准。
They're not saying is the right way,
it's certainly not standard.
我不是建议你用这个，但是
And I would not be
suggesting you use this but
这将会成为真正发生事情的答案
it's gonna turn out to be the answer
to what's really happening
当我们用标准的方法达到同样的目标时。
when we do use the standard way
of achieving this same goal.
因为标准的方式，解决方案三，解决方案四，越来越公正的解决方案四,
Cuz the standard way, solution three and
four, increasingly just solution four,
在幕后操纵这一切。
behind the scenes is doing all this here.
这意味着如果你要调试，你必须理解它。
And that means if you've gotta debug,
you've gotta understand it.
这意味着，如果你想采访和回答问题，什么是新的关键字
That means if you wanna interview and
answer the question what's the new keyword
真正的幕后工作，你得知道所有这些东西。
actually doing behind the scenes,
you got to know all this stuff.
我要说的是如果你在写作,
And I will say this, if you're writing,
如果你用这种思维方式来思考,
if once you start thinking in this
paradigm in this way of thinking,
你开始组织你所做的一切，作为对象包含
you start structuring everything
you do as object containing
与该功能及其相关功能相关的数据。
the data that's pertinent to that feature
and its associated functionality.
你解决的问题有用户、管理员、版主和测验问题,
You solving have users and admins,
and moderators, and quiz questions,
还有排名表，甚至游戏应用程序本身。
and league tables, and
even the game application itself.
一切都只是与之相关的数据的集合，但是
All is just a collection of
data associated with that but
甚至是棋盘,
even the game board,
游戏板的尺寸，然后与游戏板相关的功能。
the dimensions of the game board and then
functionality related to that game board.
我用这种方式处理所有的事情。
I use something for
everything in this way.
所以你开始写很多这样的函数来产生一个对象,
So you start writing a lot of these
functions that produce an object,
有时一个对象只有一个函数
sometimes just one object with
just a sort of functions and
你以前只有一个，从现在开始你就这么想吧。
you only ever have one of them,
you just think in this manner from now on.
所以我想如果你总是在里面创造一个小物体，总是让你的
So I guess if you're always creating
a little object inside, always making your
连接到一个函数存储，总是返回那个对象，我猜
connection to a store of functions, always
returning that object out like, I guess it
也许每次在这个过程中都能有办法拯救自己会更好。
might be nice to have a way of saving
yourself during that process every time.
但这种方式是超级复杂的，但它不是标准的。
But it is super sophisticated this way,
but it isn't standard.
所以我们现在要看到，在解决方案三，更标准的方式
So we're now gonna see in solution
three the more standard way
介绍一下关键词，他们是所有的努力工作，它的新。
introducing the keyword, they're all
that makes the hard work, its new.